How did the customer want himself during all
these years that you lived at
Lamborghini?
It's gotten younger, there are
many more of them, we have
global customers, so I can't say there is a
typical customer, but I gather from them all the
Made in Italy fact, that they love
sports cars and that they are obviously
people who are very involved in
today's world, they are entrepreneurs,
many are self-made men, so they know what we
do because very often
they also have similar experiences.  Have you
ever had any crazy anecdotes with one
of your clients?
There are many.  One of the things that stuck with me
was someone saying,
"I worked as a bean counter," so being a
controller for many years was a job I did
n't like, but it was so I could
afford a Lamborghini.  Yeah.